好的 Amy 我就去告诉以色列人让他们让让 因为他们就喜欢这样
Sure, Amy, I'll just tell the Israelis to move on, 'cause they love that.
好吧 Richard 你得把Ben的安定藏起来
All right, Richard, you need to hide Ben's Ativan
直到他把Bill Ericsson的事全坦白了
till he comes clean about Bill Ericsson.
-嗨 Amy -Bill 见..见到你真好啊
- Hi, Amy. - Bill, it... it's good to see you.
-我听说你在...-在白宫工作 对的
- I hear you're working... - Working at the White House. Yes, I am.
-什么职位? -什么职位?
- In what capacity? - What capacity?
我有一个特别的头衔 不过管得很宽
I have a specific title, but a wide brief...
消除弱点
Eliminate weaknesses.
有点儿纳粹医生的感觉
That's a little Nazi doctor.
我是传媒部门的新领导
I'm the new director of communications.
哦 不错啊 因为某些人以为
Oh, that's cool, 'cause some of us thought
你是新的竞选经理呢
you were the new campaign manager.
-嗯! -哦 不 我懂了 好的
- Mmm! - Oh, no. I get it. Okay.
好吧 我只是想用不那么友好的方式友好的打个招呼
Well, I just wanted to say a friendly hello in an unfriendly way.